Justina, Lady Elaine’s death is truly grievous,
but arresting the Tears of Blood on that alone
seems excessive.
I am well aware. I will accept whatever punishment
the Great Priestess imposes upon me. However...
What is it?
Because I had doubts about why they went there...
That's why I made that absurd claim and
carried out the arrests.
Since you, Great Priestess, and Calintz are close,
I thought perhaps he might open up to you right away.
I don't know the details, but the Hero of Water
was an immortal being. There is no way the
Tears of Blood had the power to bring such a person to death.
It's highly likely that someone else interviewed,
and the Tears of Blood were just pawns.
In the end, Calintz didn't say a single word to me.
He said he would accept whatever judgment was passed,
but that is no reason to hold him here.
Indeed, Calintz’s recent conduct is highly questionable.
Therefore, Justina, I must ask that you remain with
the Tears of Blood and watch over him closely.
Lest he fall into anything dangerous.‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎
To me, the boy is no different from my own son,
just as Agreian is.
Understood.
Lady Ladrinne?